<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tags on</title><link>/en/</link><description>Recent content in Tags on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year} Razon Yang. All Rights Reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 18:04:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>pre-commit hooks</title><link>/en/posts/pre-commit-hooks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 18:04:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/posts/pre-commit-hooks/</guid><description>Git hooks and pre-commit Client-side git hooks are custom scripts designed to fire off when some operations happen like committing or merging. They allow use to identify simple issues before submitting our code for review. Our code review will then be able to focus on the actual code rather than styling issues.
The limitation of hooks is that they are difficult to share across projects. You have to manually change them to make them work with your project structure.</description></item><item><title>Python Conventions</title><link>/en/posts/python-conventions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 13:33:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/posts/python-conventions/</guid><description>PEP 8 or How to Make your Code Readable Why is code readability and consistency that important?
Because &amp;ldquo;Code is read much more often than it is written.” as Guido van Rossum (creator of the Python programming language) said. Usually you write a piece of code once and never touch it again. But you’ll probably get back to it several times since it’s now part of your project and each time you will have to remember how it works and what it does.</description></item><item><title>Menu</title><link>/en/docs/menu/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 17:25:20 +0800</pubDate><guid>/en/docs/menu/</guid><description>&lt;p>We predefined two types of menus: &lt;code>main&lt;/code> and &lt;code>footer&lt;/code>, represents the top app bar menus and the footer menus, respectively.
This article will briefly introduce how to use the menus.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>About</title><link>/en/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/about/</guid><description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
https://github.</description></item><item><title>Contact Us</title><link>/en/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/contact/</guid><description/></item><item><title>FAQs</title><link>/en/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/faq/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Offline</title><link>/en/offline/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/offline/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>